Jenessa White

612-244-5774 | jenessawhite.com | jenessaw31@gmail.com | Github: @jenessawhite

Skills

HTML/CSS | JavaScript/jQuery | React/React-Native | Git/Github | WordPress | NodeJS

Summary

Instilled with a passion for bringing beauty and ideal user experience to the web, I'm a software engineer with a frontend focus. Using the suite of skills that I am continuously developing, I strive to bring positive and unique ideas that will enhance the products and services that we provide. My experience in customer service has provided me with an advantageous understanding of UI/UX.

Experience

Front End Engineering Student

October 2016 - January 2017

The Iron Yard

- Participating in a 12-week immersive Front End Engineering program.
- Developing essential development skills, HTML/CSS, JS, jQuery, etc.
- Learning best practices and principles for both team and solo work.
- Producing a multiple web/mobile apps that use React, React-Native & vanilla JS

MDU Representative

May 2016 - September 2016

DIRECTV

- Provided customer with technical solutions for their DIRECTV equipment.
- Coordinated with Research & Resolution and Tier 2 Technical Support teams on more complex issues.
- Protected customer's financial and personal data by adhering to the highest standards of security.
- Handled 20-40 customer calls/requests a day.

Registration Consultant

June 2015 - May 2016

SportsEngine

- Worked directly with clients to plan on how to meet needs and goals for their registration systems.
- Built registration forms on the SportsEngine platform for clients.
- Organized, revised and updated information on SportsEngine websites and registrations.

Content Specialist

August 2014 - June 2015

SportsEngine

- Built hundreds of registration pages for Jr. PGA League camps.
- Assisted in managing Buckeye CableSystem Sports Network (BCSN)/The Toledo Blade preps sports section.
- Entered statistical data utilizing SportsEngine Mass Score software for a variety of events.

Education

Bachelor of Science (BS) - University of Minnesota-Twin Cities

2009 - 2014